Wrong place. Wrong crime.
Dead of Winter is a thriller film directed by Brian Kirk.
A widowed fisherwoman, travelling alone through snowbound northern
Minnesota, interrupts the kidnapping of a teenage girl.
Hours from the nearest town and with no phone service, she
realizes that she is the young girl's only hope.
Barb, played by Emma Thompson.
Purple Lady, played by Judy Greer.
Camo Jacket, played by Marc Menchaca.
Leah, played by Laurel Marsden.
Young Barb, played by Gaia Wise.
Young Karl, played by Cúán Hosty-Blaney.
Dead of Winter is a 2025 psychological thriller film directed by Brian Kirk
and written by Nicholas Jacobson-Larson and Dalton Leeb.
It stars Emma Thompson, Judy Greer, Marc Menchaca, and Laurel Marsden.
The film had its world premiere in the Piazza Grande section of the 78th Locarno Film
Festival on August 8, 2025, before its theatrical release on September 26, 2025.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, minnesota, fisherman, snow, cabin.
The tone is intense.